Procheta Nag

Designer | Researcher

pnag@sfu.ca

□ 778 222 1311



PROJECTS

Grad Society Website

UX Designer

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021 | Simon Fraser University, Vancouver, BC

I was responsible for User research, Taxonomy hierarchy, Site map, Information architeture, User flow, Wireframes, Low to high fidelity prototype, Usability test in order to redesign the simon fraser university grad society website.

ALEXA AI

Personal project

I have conceptualize updated features with amazon alexa app following primary and secondary research, research synthesis, user flow, wireframe, prototype.

CUPCAKE CRAVE

Personal project

I have designed an online cupcake store website following user research, product roadmap, empathy map, customer journey map, user flow, sitemap, wireframe, prototype.

EXPERIENCE

Simon Fraser University

Graduate Teaching Assistant

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 | Vancouver, BC

I have taught followings to undergraduate students -

- Site Maps, User Flow, Wireframes, Card sorting, Personas, Low to High Fidelity Prototyping in Axure, Origami Studio.
- Responsive website design with HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Kinetic Typography, Motion Graphics, Storyboarding in Adobe Photoshop, After Effect, Premiere Pro.

Simon Fraser University

Graduate Research Assistant

Jan 2019 - Aug 2020 | Vancouver, BC

• Designed interactive conversation system with embodied virtual agent. Evaluated research study by adopting wide ranges of Qualitative and Quantitative research methods and tools.

A2i - Prime Minister's Office

User Experience Intern

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017 | Bangladesh

• Performed usability testing, A/B testing of websites, generated improved design idea, document improved design concept.

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University

M.Sc. In Human Computer Intercation (HCI)

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 | Vancouver, BC

Thesis: Design embodied virtual agent and evaluate the effect of gender during the intercation with Virtual Agent.

Khulna University

B.Sc. In Computer Science & Engineering (CSE)

Aug 2013 - Dec 2017 | Bangladesh

Thesis: Develop holistic user centric framework to predict acute mayocardial infaraction using data mining and real world data.

SKILLS

Research		Design	
User Interviews		Prototypying	
Contextual Inquiry		Wireframing	
Quantitative Surveys		Information Architecture	
Statistical Analysis		Sitemap, Sketch	
Heuristic Evaluation		Empathy Map	
Usability Testing		User Journey, User Flow	
A/B Testing		Persona	s, Storyboarding
Tools			Development
Figma	SPSS		HTML
Axure	Zeplin		CSS
Adobe XD	Balsam	niq	Bootstrap
Origami Studio)		Javascript

ACOMPLISHMENTS

Adobe Creative Suite

- SFU TMRA Award 2020
- 1st Runner Up National Women Hacathon,
 2017

Latex

- Service Innovation Fund (Round 9), 2017
- Winner Women Innovation Camp, Prime

Minister's Office, 2016

• B.Sc. Scholarship, 2015